Dear little Bronny, what to say to you?
You have my eyes, you also have my name
When you made it to the league I cried
Couldn’t wait to start
Now I get to practice every day with you
The rookie life… for me it's been a while
Back in Ohio, I always knew you'd be a star
And to me that's what you are
You will come of age with our young players
One day you’ll lead a team
Like me back in ‘16
If you just keep silencing the haters
Oh it would be a dream, LeGoat is in your genes
And you'll blow us all away
Bronny, Bronny
Yeah, you'll blow us all away
Oh, Bronny, when you play oh I just squirm
LeSperm, look at LeSperm
Pride is not the word I'm looking for
There is so much more inside me now
Ooh, Bronny, just make sure that handle’s firm
LeSperm
When you play, here’s what I see
It's like watching a young me
My father wasn't around (my father wasn't around)
I swear that I'll be around for you
I did my best just to teach (took my talents to south beach )
I’ll make sure one day you’re crowned king too
You will come of age with our young players
One day you’ll lead a team
Like me back in ‘16
If you just keep silencing the haters
Oh it would be a dream, LeGoat is in your genes
And you'll blow us all away
Bronny, Bronny
Yeah, you'll blow us all away